



Brooklyn NY



6466528972



alexisjordan842@gmail.com alexisjordan842@yahoo.co m



https://jordan721.github.io /Jordan\_Alexis/ https://www.linkedin.com/i n/jordan-alexis-799214175/

Skills & Specialization:
Microsoft Word, Microsoft
PowerPoint, Microsoft Excel,
Microsoft Outlook, Adobe
Photoshop, Adobe Premiere, Adobe
XD, Adobe InDesign, Adobe
Illustrator, HTML/CSS, PHP,
Responsive Design, Data Entry,
jQuery

# Jordan Alexis

## **About Me:**

I have experience using programming languages such as HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Cloud Computing, and others to help build websites for clients or myself.

Experience using Adobe Creative Cloud applications such as Premiere, PhotoShop, Illustrator, InDesign, and XD to help make my websites and other jobs I must do.

Experience entering client information into a database and checking the information is secured and correct. Dealing with customers who need help with orders placed or account information.

# **Experience**

#### July 2021-Aug 2021

Software Engineer • Unadat • New York, NY (US)

- •Led a cross-functional team to develop a dark mode for the Unadat portal site
- •Optimized dark theme for the mobile and progressive web app.
- •Coordinated efforts of the design team in devising and user testing the color scheme and functionality.
- Debugged independent research to overcome roadblocks and obstacles.

#### Jan 2019-May 2019

Spring Intern • WBAI Radio 99.5FM NYC • Brooklyn, NY (US)

- •Assisted in Sorting and Mailing out prizes for their WBAI Buddies.
- •Managed their social media Using Hootsuite
- Assigned managing some Customer Service tasks.
- Assisted in their event calendar by using Photoshop to make the pictures for each article presentable.
- •Assisted in entering important personal data for their WBAI Buddies.

#### Jul 2018-Aug 2018

Multimedia Internship • The Challenge Publisher Group • Brooklyn, NY (US)

- Assisted in creating a modernized version of a newspaper called "The New American" by making it in Adobe InDesign from scratch.
- •I Used Photoshop to make images given to me more presentable.
- •Distributed the Newspaper to the boroughs of New York.



#### Aug 2017-Aug 2017

SYEP • Office Assistant • Brooklyn, NY (US)

- Assisted in handling/transferring calls to the site managers and Interns.
- Handing of entering data for payroll and time spent working at job sites.
- Handling Information to see if the applicants/Inters were still working and checking on their performance review.

## Jul 2017-Aug 2017

Multimedia Developer Internship • St. John's Recreation Center • Brooklyn, NY (US)

- •Learned about Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign effectively.
- •Learned how to record audio using GarageBand and using audio to create a 3-5-minute video using Windows Media Player.

#### July 2014-Aug 2014

Day Care Worker • Charles Churn Christian Academy • Brooklyn, NY (US)

- •Assisted in making sure the children (5-10) went to their destinations safely.
- •Assisted in making activities, and organized the work and camp environment.
- •Carried equipment to wherever they needed to be.

# **Education**

## Brooklyn College, Brooklyn NY, Aug 2019 - Presently Enrolled

 Bachelor's Degree, Multimedia Computing and Computer Science

# Borough of Manhattan Community College, Manhattan NY, Aug 2017 – May 2019

Associate degree, Multimedia Programming, and Design

## Technical Career Institute, Manhattan NY, Jan 2017 – May 2017

 Associate degree, Credits Towards Computer Systems Networking and Telecommunications

## Bramson Ort College, Queens NY, Oct 2014 - Jan 2017

 Associate degree, Credits Towards Computer Information Systems (Game Design Concertation)